LISHA PAYNE

bigt00fgrin@gmail.com / Brooklyn, NY 11220 lishap.github.io/portfolio

SKILLS

Mac OS & Windows. Adobe Creative Suite, Figma, GitHub. Experience with WordPress, HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Java, p5.js and C++. Comfortable with hand, power and machine woodworking tools. Analog and digital photography, processing, scanning and enlarger/ink jet printing & screen printing.

TRAINING
AND
EDUCATION

The Rabbit 2023, Game Development Residency Medienboard Berlin-Brandenburg, Germany

Interactive Media Arts B.F.A
New York University's Tisch School Of The Arts
3.8, graduated cum laude

SHOWS

Berlin's Amaze Open Screens 2023 BAMkids' Film Festival 2019

WORK EXPERIENCE

Ask me about my 6+ years of retail, bar and dining customer service experience!

BEAM CENTER

Summer Program Designer

June 2023 → August 2023 in Brooklyn, NY

- Developed 6-week curriculum on Play Structures for students and teachers.
- Inventoried materials and equipment for 195 students across 6 schools.
- Supported teachers in the classroom to instruct building, soldering and crafting.

INTERACTIVE
TELE
COMMUNICATIONS
PROGRAM AT NYU

Floor Staff

September 2018 → May 2022 in Brooklyn, NY

- Checked in and out audio, visual and electronic equipment to students, residents and faculty, over 50x per day.
- Organized and inventoried equipment in 15+ equipment cages and classrooms.
- Provided support for faculty and students in managing, learning, and using equipment by explaining the proper use, assisting with proper hookup and helping students and faculty to troubleshoot equipment problems.

LEX

Product Design Intern

October 2018 → August 2021 in New York, NY

- Formatting and reworked copy for personal ads, 50x per day.
- Assisted with design of user interface for iOS and Android for the beta mobile application.
- Front-end web design and copywriting for the company website.
- Managed a bug logging and reporting system for the product manager to log bugs in the app and send them to a developer, 25x per day.

WHEELHOUSE CREATIVE

Production and Editing Assistant

August 2017 → June 2022 in New York, NY

- Logged dailies 20x per day for the feature film, The World Before Your Feet (2018), executively produced by Jesse Eisenberg and directed by Jeremy Workman.
- · Assisted on production for both on-location and studio sets
- Edited sequences using Adobe Premiere to create rough cuts